Every character that you play as an artist, I think that you lend yourself to the craft.
There are definitely things that I have lent of myself to creating the character.
But I'm not non-binary in life.
I am gay.
I also felt that I had the right as a gay man to be able to play and portray a member of my community that was a part of the LGBTQ+.
If I did not, by that line of logic, I would never be able to play King Lear.
And then I said, oh, actually I would because my father was a prince.
So I have a royal line.
Welcome to the winter of our discontent.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
And I think that you have to be able to know yourself and as an artist, explore.
So I went shopping.